intelligentedu.com 2005-03-08

# Intelligentedu.com Privacy Policy

**Learn New Skills & Increase Your Earning Power With FREE Computer Training!**

Learn programming for Free and how to develop and write computer programs and IT applications. Get Free knowledge, information, references, and resources about computers now. Many **Free** training courses, tutorials, books, training guides, tips, articles, and helps are available to you. 

For help finding what you need go to Navigation by Topic to Free Training or use pop-up.

 **Subscribe to our Free semimonthly Newsletter to Get the Latest & Best FREE Computer IT Training!** \- You'll stay current with all the New Free Computer Training and Education sites we discover - Subscribe now because you'll have access to these great new sites a month before our web site visitors do, and with each issue you'll receive our 2 non-public links containing 97 Pages of Free Training with _over 10,000_ Free IT training and tutorial resources. Plus, you'll receive our new 21 chapter e-book "Understanding Computer Security" for Free!

**I.T. Education & Training:**

 **Home Page**

 **Free Computer Training & Courses**

 **Free Computer Books**

 **Free Tutorials, Guides, Support & Help**

 **Free University Course Websites**

 **Best FREE Online Computer IT Courses**

 **Lower Fee Distance Learning Sites**

 **Higher Fee Distance Learning Sites**

 **Link and Resource Sites**

 **Free Certification Exam Study Guides**

 **Free IT Training Tutorials**

 **Free IT Training Downloads**

 **Monthly Newsletter: New Free Sites**

 **IT Sites Worth Mentioning**

 **Free Site of the Month**

 **Best Course & Degree Locators**

 **Free Desktop & Office Tutorials**

 **Link To This Site**

 **Additional Site Content:**

 **Member Info & Sign Up**

 **Member Login**

 **IT Certification Counselor and Complete List**

 **Financial Aid Resources**

 **Online IT Publications**

 **IT Associations & Organizations**

 **The Latest Technology News**

 **Online Games**

 **Music and Movies**

 **Travel Reservations, Flight Schedules & Tracking**

 **The Best of the Web**

 **Best Developer Books at Amazon.com**

 **How You Can Support Our IT Training Mission**

##### **Community Content:**

 **Tell a Friend about this Site**   

**  
   
 Make us your homepage! (IE only)| 

> > | 
>> 
>>  **Privacy Policy of Intelligentedu.com**  
>>   
>> ---  
>>  
>>> This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for [http://www.intelligentedu.com](http://www.intelligentedu.com/). If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you can contact Scott Turton at [scott_turton@intelligentedu.com](mailto:scott_turton@intelligentedu.com).
>>> 
>>> We collect email address information volunteered by our visitors, for our free, opt-in monthly newsletter. We display ads using the services of websponsors.com and cj.com.
>>> 
>>> We respect the privacy of our **Newsletter** subscribers, it is our policy:
>>> 
>>>   *  **Opt-in Subscription**. Our newsletter subscribers "opt-in" with their reply to our confirming email. The email address information we collect is used to notify our opt-in subscribers about updates to our Web site.
>>> 
>>>   *  **Choice and consent.** To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request.
>>> 
>>>   *  **Third party use.** To not sell, rent, or loan our subscriber or customer lists to third parties for commercial purposes . While we may sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we do not allow third parties any other use of these subscriber lists.
>>> 
>>>   *  **Unsubscriptions.** To send our periodicals only to those who request them, and immediately unsubscribe those who request it. Every issue of our free newsletter explains how to subscribe and unsubscribe at the bottom, or you can go here.
>>> 
>>> 

>>> 
>>>  **Cookies.** To use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. We use cookies to help with advertising, We do NOT collect or use information from cookies to develop a profile about our visitors and customers.
>>> 
>>>  **Security.** To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, or behind password protection, or off-line.
>>> 
>>>  **Termination**. If a majority portion of the assets of Intelligentedu.com were to be acquired by another organization, that might include our subscriber and other lists, but only as part of a clear agreement binding that organization to abide by the spirit and letter of our privacy policy
>>> 
>>>  **Access to Information**. Upon request we provide site subscribers, members, and customers with their unique identifier information (e.g., site member user id and passcode) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.
>>> 
>>>  **Links**. The links to other Internet sites on Intelligentedu.com are provided as a service to our web site visitors, based on information from the internet and the web sites listed. Intelligentedu.com and Scott Turton are not responsible for the content of these listings, nor does it endorse any claims made. We encourage all of our partners, contributors and third parties to implement policies and practices that respect the privacy of our users. However, Intelligentedu.com, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 
>>> 
>>> From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.
>>> 
>>> We review our privacy practices from time to time, and our practices are subject to change. We ask that our visitors periodically review this page to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our privacy statement.  
>>   
>>  Return to Top   
>  Back to previous page   
>   
>>   
>>   * .
>> 
>> 

> 
>     
>   
>   
>
